-*- 用热情教学 -*-
I think that passion is one of the few things
我认为热情是为数不多的
that would take you into a vocation like teaching
让你进入教师这类职业的特质之一，
which is generally so thankless
教师通常都是吃力不讨好，
and so demanding and so underpaid
要求很高、报酬很低，
and so poorly valued in the society.
而且其价值被社会严重低估。
Passion is what most good teachers have in their guts
热情是大多数优秀老师的本能，
it's what makes them want to go into a classroom
这就是为什么他们愿意走进教室
and serve the young.
并为年轻人服务。
And it's not passion about going to a school of education
这不是因为去学校这件事有热情，
which is often a very passionless place.
因为那里通常是个非常没有热情的地方。
It's passion about children,
这事关对儿童的热爱，
it's passion about young lives
事关对年轻生命的热爱，
it's passion about helping those young lives
事关对帮助年轻生命
to flower and grow
绽放和成长的热爱，
and it's often passion about a subject
而且往往事关对某个学科的热爱,
maybe good literature
也许是优秀文学作品,
or physical or natural science or history.
也许是物理学或自然科学或历史学。
A lens through which you can see the world
通过学科这个镜头，你可以看到这个世界，
and a lens which for this teacher has
对这位教师来说，通过学科这个镜头，
given him or her a broader view of the world，
让他或她对世界的了解有了更广阔的视角，
a richer view of the world in a larger sense of self.
在更大的自我意识中，对世界有了更丰富的看法。
And the teacher is passionate about wanting to help
老师热情帮助年轻人
some young people see the world through that lens
通过这些镜头了解这个世界，
and enlarge their own sense of selfhood.
并扩展他们的自我意识。
So passion is right at the heart of good teaching.
总而言之，热情是优秀教学的核心。